NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING THE
FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
What’s your final decision, brother?
Did you come to a conclusion?
You disobeyed the orders once again,
Osman Bey.
You will get arrested.
Who is going to do that, brother?
Alps!
Arrest him!
In the name of Allah!
Don’t you dare!
I’m talking to you Alps!
Sheathe your swords!
May you not stir up trouble, Bamsı Bey!
I’m the Head Alp here!
Savcı Bey, the Head Alp.
Oh folks!
Listen to me!
If you want to see a Head Alp…
… look right here!
However, if you want to see the Kayı Bey…
… look right there!
He is the one who took your prisoner
brothers back...
... while you were busy talking here!
Who can say a word to him now?
I can!
You huh?
Yes, me!
Enough!
Enough already!
I’m your big brother!
Osman, you will not stand against the
Head Alp!
And Savcı, you will not will arrest your
brother because of this reason!
Brother!
You were giving me lectures about being
a brother!
Take your hands off my brother!
Savcı Bey, hurry up!
Our Bey is dying!
Our father is dying!
Father.
Whatever happens, they are brothers.
They are the sons of Ertuğrul Gazi.
There are news from our spies in Black
Sea region.
Supporting forces are coming to
Kulacahisar.
Ertuğrul is on his death bed and his sons
are fighting for Beyhood.
With this news, he may pretty well be
dead by now.
Soon, you will get the revenge of your
father from the Turks.
After you hear your new duty, you will
thank me since I dissuaded you from death.
Just like Caesar during the battle of
Axona...
… you will kill every Turk you see.
With pleasure, Nikola.
Thinking that we would attack, they
increased their defence.
But Osman saw what I am able to do.
With the forces coming to Kulacahisar…
… we will bite them like a snake at an
unexpected time.
2 DAYS LATER
Don’t be hard on yourself.
Who knows, maybe he will stand up like
nothing has happened.
Isn’t it possible, Osman?
He is sleeping all day.
I’ve never seen my father like that
before.
All he is doing is puking blood.
Osman.
What about my brother?
He was going to arrest me.
You listen to nobody's words, Osman.
You always do you.
Everything happens because of this reason.
You are too aggressive.
When you are angry, you become unbearable.
-You are too aggressive and…
-My Bala.
Have I sickened you?
You are never free from troubles, my
Osman.
Please continue.
Are there more things you want to say?
Indeed there are.
I’m also dragged after those troubles.
Have I really tortured you this much?
Of course not, the real torture starts if
I’m not dragged after those very troubles.
I can give my life for the troubles
you bring.
My Bala…
… my Savcı brother is being provoked by
Yalvak.
He is using my brother and uncle against
me.
You should talk to your brother.
I can try but he has become blind as to
his ambitions.
However, it can’t continue like this.
Will he listen to me if I suggest
him to go to Kulacahisar together?
He will say we should wait to get
stronger.
However, those mischiefs, Nikola and
Flatyos...
… are they going to wait?
No, they are not going to.
And I’m not going to wait either.
I’m going to kill both of them!
I will enter that castle and cut their
their throats!
How are you going to enter that castle?
I’ll manage, my Bala!
Among all those soldiers, how are you
going to manage that?
Please hold your horses, Osman.
It’s not the time to wait, my Bala.
Since the fall of Kulacahisar, the time
has been ticking against us.
They will become stronger once
they get support from Constantinople.
When that happens, how are we going to
find support?
My Bey, Zulfikar brother brought
important news.
Tell me, Zulfikar!
Osman Bey, the supporting forces have
arrived at Kulacahisar.
Who are they and how many of them there
are?
I don’t know their numbers but they are
all cavaliers.
Kuman cavaliers.
Kuman Turks?
They are pitting brothers against
brothers.
There are traitors among them, my Bey!
It's obvious that they were tricked by
golds.
But…
Tell me.
Those traitors betrayed their own Bey too.
They killed him and captured his daughter.
Nikola’s men are taking her to the castle
at the moment.
Why did they kill their Bey?
Because he refused to fight against us,
my Bey.
Before she enters the pit of Devil, we
must save her.
We are ready, my Bey.
As you can see Bala, it’s not the time
to wait.
You shall go to Tent with Zulfikar.
I won’t wait to fight.
My Bala, listen to Selcan Hatun and may
your eyes be wide open.
Let’s go!
Please sit down, my Bey.
You are spinning my head.
They think Osman will do what is said.
They are telling me stop.
How can they be this blind?
He is becoming worse day by day!
You know he can’t stand Yalvak Arslan.
He loses his mind to his anger whenever
Yalvak is here.
He must be suspecting he’s trying to
deceive us.
Is there someone who doesn’t play games in
these lands, Lena?
Perhaps, he has other plans.
He wants the Kayı Tent by his side.
And be sure of Kayı Tent.
Only then, he will cooperate with us.
Instead of deceiving us, he wants to
deceive our enemies together.
However, my brother keeps ruining
everything.
Is there anything I can do, my Bey?
I’d like to support you.
Keep an eye on Bala Hatun.
Report me every step Selcan and Bala Hatun
will take.
I’m going to stand against everyone who
stand against you.
I will do more things than just
reporting you.
I will control the Hatuns of this Tent
from now on.
How are you going to do that?
Do I ask you how you are managing things?
I will go the Tent of Yalvak Arslan now.
Nobody should know.
Is Osman coming with you?
No.
He hasn’t been informed.
How is he doing?
He is burning like a flame.
I sent my Alps to the best physicians.
They will be here soon.
Ertuğrul Bey is like a half-father for me.
I can’t stand seeing him in this
condition.
May Allah bless you.
I know how much you like your
brother, Dündar.
I’m aware of your pain and sorrow.
But it’s important to be ready for
everything.
It’s haram for us, Beys, to cry after our
loved ones.
What are you saying?
Ertuğrul Bey is not only our loved one but
the one who balances all Tents and powers.
With him, comes the peace.
I know how hard it is to replace him.
However, I want you to know that I’ll
stand by your side with this situation.
I’m going to cut your throats once you
open the cage!
You null slaves!
Those who dare to fetter lions will be the
victim of claws!
Open the cage!
I said open it!
She must be the one Zulfikar told us
about.
Where are they headed, my Bey?
We will learn now.
You stay here.
Stop!
Who are you?
Osman, Ertuğrul Gazi’s son.
Set her free.
We were looking for you in the sky but we
found you here.
Your sword is sharp, Bey’s daughter.
So you are Osman Bey whom they even
fear you name.
Yes, it’s me.
You didn’t ask but I’ll tell you anyways.
I’m Targun Hatun.
What business Kuman Turks have here?
They came here to fight for the Emperor.
They are going to attack you with Nikola
and Flatyos.
From where they will attack?
You need to figure that out yourself,
Osman Bey.
I shall go now.
Stop.
Stop!
You are right. I forgot to thank you.
You should thank to Allah, Targun Hatun.
Your father was killed as he didn’t want
to attack us.
And they caged you because of this reason.
I see you already know everything, Osman
Bey.
What else do you want from me?
Your life is an escrow for us from now on.
I can guard my life by my own, Osman Bey.
You shouldn’t bother.
I don’t have the time to argue!
Listen to my words!
We should go to the Tent.
Though our religions are different, we
both come from Oghuz lineage.
You are right, Osman Bey.
Our veins share the same blood.
You will be our guest.
Also, you have a wound which needs to be
taken care of.
Nothing but a scratch.
It needs to be stigmatized.
Let’s go.
Valiants!
From now on, you can’t take a break to
drink water.
Not even to breath!
Your swords should be sharp so that they
can kill forty soldiers with one swing!
Come on, Valiants!
You are not allowed to make mistakes!
Stand straight!
May your steps be strong!
The time of many battles has come!
Yeah, just like this!
We must execute even the easiest
task with such care!
Go now!
Do you all understand?
-Yes, our Bey!
-Don't worry, our Bey!
My Bey, as you ordered, we surrounded the
Tent with a huge wall made out of spears.
With Allah's permisson, even a fly
can't breach it.
Thank you, my Ayaz.
You should also remove all the bridges
there are on the ditches.
After all, even a single mistake can bring
the end of our Tent.
Go now, Valiant.
As you order, my Bey.
Bamsı Bey, the archers are on their
position and we doubled their numbers.
How wonderful, my lion Valiant!
Go to your position now.
How magnificent!
Do you like your place?
I think it’s pretty good.
Nikola, Osman has just saved Targun Hatun.
He is Osman and he is capable of doing
such things.
He’s taking her to the Tent.
Wouldn’t you do the same thing if you
were him, Flatyos?
You know what they say.
Osman took the bait.
Open your eyes wide open.
I heard you need our help, Nikola.
So, after all, the Emperor sent you?
He knows we fight better than the Romans.
He sent his best units.
Looks like he believes in you.
You must be their
leader since he sent you.
Have no doubt.
Targun. You and Kayıs share ancestors, you
wouldn't also act like them, would you?
Don't worry, Nikola. We're used
to doing what the Romans can't.
This duty is more
dangerous than before.
Are you having fun?
As long as you're in my arms like this,
I'd always have fun.
If you don't free my father immediately,
your life will be hell!
I'll free your father
if you can complete your duty.
- What duty?
- Prisoner duty.
- Who will I capture?
- Yourself. You'll be like your father.
I'm used to working with my sword.
Your mind is as sharp as your sword.
I want the Kayıs to know that.
Mighty Ceasar.
This is our first step.
It'The time for revenge
is close, father!
Hazal...
You'll pay for what you've done!
I’ve decided to wait for Aygül to be okay…
… and not tell anyone while doing it.
But I had to come after
hearing about Ertuğrul Bey.
Bala?
Bala, my daughter.
Are you okay?
You’re really inspecting those carpets.
Nothing. I’m just daydreaming.
If you don’t let it out,
your troubles will grow on the inside.
Tell your mother about it.
I’m worrying about Osman, mother.
What about Osman?
He went to rescue a woman.
What’s wrong with that?
Shouldn’t every valiant
fight for the good of the poor?
That’s right.
But there’s something in my heart.
I’ll come another time.
It’s okay, daughter.
Is he sleeping?
Mashallah!
What is that for?
You go, Selcan mother.
I’ll look after the baby.
Thank you.
Welcome my Bey.
We have company.
Just a guest.
Aunt.
My valiant!
Glad you came. We couldn’t
find time to chat with you.
We’ll eventually do it, son.
Who’s this lady?
Daughter of a
Bey running away from cruelty.
Welcome. Don’t feel like a guest. You’re
one of us now. Feel like our daughter.
Thank you. I know how
hospitable Kayıs are.
You’ve rescued a prisoner.
Give me a tent and I’ll support you too.
Bala. Take care of our guest.
She’s wounded.
Of course, my Bey.
Aunt.
Such a guest won’t
leave so easily, my Bala.
I’ve something to tell you.
I wonder what it is. Tell me, son.
She’s our guest. But…
… keep your eye on her.
Are you suspicious of something.
Being suspicious is a must for me, aunt.
It is indeed. Don’t worry.
I’ll take care of her.
Thank you.
My Bey! News from Kumral Abdal.
What is it?
They found Cerkutay’s trace.
Cerkutay!
They saw them running away
from Nökers near İnegöl.
Get him immediately. So that we can
see what tricks they’re playing.
Okay, my Bey.
Cerkutay!
No one will be able to save you from me.
It is time to pay, Hazal!
It is time to pay!
I’m waiting for Ertuğrul Bey to open his
eyes like I’m waiting for some good news.
I can’t wait for him to open his eyes
and say “Abdurrahman! Be ready!”.
But our Bey’s state isn’t good.
If it was someone else,
he’d be dead by now.
I think he has something left to do
since he’s fighting death for us.
My mighty Bey!
He won’t give up so easily.
He has things to do
and battles to fight.
Friends! Duties don’t wait,
battles don’t end!
You don’t oppose
the act of Allah!
Lives are temporary. You don’t
complain while giving them back.
Kayı Tent is under control
of those who support Yavlak.
While my father is fighting for his life…
... Kayı’s cause is humiliated
by a fool named Yavlak.
Dündar Bey is Ertuğrul Bey’s brother.
Gündüz and Savcı Bey are their sons.
They won’t pursue this
mistake, Inshallah.
I’ll bring them back from this mistake.
May it be easy.
Our Hatuns are quite skilled.
Fine craftsmanship.
Why are you all around the guest?
You should let her breathe.
Bala. Our guest’s wound
needs to be seared.
- I can do that!
- Bala will do it.
You can take care of Ertuğrul Bey.
Don’t worry, mother.
I’ve heard about Kayı carpets.
I could finally see them.
Mashallah! Our name is heard
all the way from there!
Bala. The wound
doesn’t wait. Let’s go.
Osman hunted
a deer this time.
The end is near.
When it takes place, I want
you all to hear my decision.
Know it, so that you can act accordingly.
When Ertuğrul Gazi, son
of Süleiman Şah, passes away…
… the throne of Beys, as his son…
… will be mine.
I’d die for you!
From now on, hogs like Geyhatu…
… rabid dogs like Nikola…
… degenerates like Yavlak won’t
be standing in our way.
Eyvallah, Osman. The castle we
conquered is on the enemy’s hands.
People will remind you that.
We need to take Kulacahisar.
You can then announce
the decision you’ve made here.
I’ll enter that castle.
If my brothers and
uncle divided Kayı…
… if I don’t have enough Alps
to reconquer that castle…
… then I’ll infiltrate the castle and
cut the throats of Nikola and Flatyos!
Osman! We don’t doubt that.
But if you’re going to be a Bey,
you shouldn’t put yourself in danger.
Don’t act before learning
what Savcı thinks.
I worry that you’ll
trip each other.
Where are my brothers and uncle?
Tell me. Why should we care about
what they think if they’re not here?
Your brothers and uncle
are in Yavlak Arslan’s pavilion.
They’re celebrating the Bey of the Beys.
What are you saying, Bamsı Bey?
Why didn’t you tell me?
Because they’re doing
something behind your back.
I didn’t want you to
do something out of anger.
They’re doing things
behind my back.
Are those who Ertuğrul Gazi’s
successors are?
Are those who will
protect Kayı’s future?
They visited Yavlak Arslan personally!
Son, they made a mistake.
They’ll eventually correct it!
- I’ll show them.
- Son! What will you show them?
One of them is your uncle,
the rest are your brothers!
Don’t make a mistake!
Bamsı Bey! Make up your mind!
Are you with me or not?
My dark-eyed Osman!
Being by your side doesn’t
mean supporting your mistakes!
Of course, we’re with you.
But it is our duty to warn you when
you’re this close to making mistakes!
We got these manners from
our ancestors, remember?
The age of brothers and uncles are over!
Following one’s feelings is over!
It’s time to be a state!
No one will be able
to stand against this cause!
Everyone will show their faces!
No one can be a Mongol and a Kayı!
No one can be a Greek and a Turk!
There can be no war and peace!
Either Turk or Mongol!
Either Kayı or Greek!
Either blasphemy or faith!
Mashallah!
It will hurt.
I don’t want it.
With the seal and
the duty we’ve received…
… we’ve our responsibilities increased.
We’ll all be relaxing if we
succeed in our responsibilities.
We’ll be free of
the Mongol’s punishments.
We’ve wasted our people
and resources in these campaigns.
Now, we need to
enter an age of peace.
As you know, the leader of Kayı’s Ertuğrul
Bey, who share borders with the greeks…
… is fighting for his life
against a deadly disease.
He’s in no shape to make decisions.
Savcı Bey, with Ertuğrul Bey’s order,
is the leader of Kayı Tent.
Beys of Kayı shall obey Savcı
like they obey Ertuğrul Gazi.
I don’t see Osman and Bamsı Bey here.
This seems like an
attitude against Savcı Bey.
Under these circumstances,
how will peace be established?
I asked Osman and
Bamsı Bey to not be here.
Neither of them will have
anything left in Kayı Tent.
Osman Bey is mad. But he’ll see
that resisting alone is not the way.
If we work together,
what can he do?
If Bamsı Bey is with him,
he’s not alone.
That means he has an army!
Osman Bey is an army on his own!
Bamsı Bey is valiant. But he’s old.
Bamsı Bey doesn’t have
a place in the future of Kayı.
My brother Osman
wants the good of Kayıs.
He wants them to grow and expand.
Remember, Beys.
He was victorious many times.
He conquered Kulacahisar.
But…
But he also saw that conquests
without solid foundations are no good.
He’ll see that you can’t
found states in one day.
- Inshallah.
He has to. We have
to be together for greater goals!
I’ll set off for Kastamonu today.
I want to see that I’m leaving
something strong behind.
I’m counting on you.
Kongar! Brother! I knew you’d come back!
Göktuğ, not Kongar!
Your death, not your brother!
You didn’t come from me?
Pity.
Death, you were saying?
Death is here, Kongar.
But not for me! For you!
What do we have here?
What are you doing
here, Flatyos?
Göktuğ is also here.
We had some accounts for calling.
It won’t take long,
Flatyos! Don’t worry!
I congratulate you for becoming
the Bey of Beys...
...but, won't there be anything done for
Kulucahisar before you return to Kastamonu?
Will Nicola the dishonorable
go unpunished?
Let's say that Osman Bey is rushing,
he is unwary...
...then, what is the measure
you are taking?
When do you want to take the castle?
It will wait. Now, nothing will be done
without Geyhatu's approval.
Of course, we'll take Kulucahisar back.
What do you think?
Yavlak Arslan has great targets.
What is Kulucahisar? If you don't defy me...
...if you follow me with your
alps in war-time...
...I can take even Bursa and İznik.
It will be that way, surely.
The dark days will be gone.
As long as we move with caution,
we can take both İznik and Bursa.
Surely, we can.
Bamsı Bey, we have orders.
Osman Bey won't be taken to the meeting.
I will enter if I want to.
Don't worry about Osman anymore.
Open the door!
Don't make me kill you.
You forgot Ertuğrul Ghazi's son Osman
Bey, and the great ghazi Bamsı Bey.
Osman! You went over your level again,
Osman! You violated the law again!
The laws? The enemy is sending the Cuman
cavalries upon us to make Turks...
...kill Turks, and you are here sitting
and eating. Is this the law?
-How do you know that?
-How do I know? I heard and confirmed it.
We will penetrate them, brother.
That's a bad ambush.
Attack!
Come on!
Wait!
We got our hunt.
We can take care of them later.
What does this dog Flatyos have
to do with Cerkutay?
Osman Bey will get mad, brother. Cerkutay
was a link to everything and we lost him.
While you are sitting here, the enemy is
preparing to strike the Kayı Tribe.
Alps.
Hold there!
Bamsı Bey! Do you know what does it mean
to draw a sword in the Bey of Beys' presence?
Bamsı Bey! You are stepping over us all.
Uncle!
Brothers!
This is the end of words.
It's time for a decision now.
You'll either stand with this Yavlak who
hides under the dresses of the Mongols...
...who work together with the heathens
that are the greatest enemies of the Turks!
Or, you will stand with me, who fights for
the holy war, who can't be stopped...
...with chains, who rathers die than
getting captured; Osman Bey!
Make your decision and pay the cost.
And about that Yavlak Arslan that
you sit at his table...
...I will expose him as well.
He'll pay for the ravens he sent after me.
Osman, know your words.
You don't have any evidence...
Enough!
How much more will you defy me, Osman?
No one will be able to stand against
the state that I will build!
What state?
What state, Osman?
The state of those who bow down to
no one but Allah...
...who don't listen to no Mongol no Rum
nor anyone else when it's about...
...the future, the freedom of the Turks!
Who believe in Allah...
...who seeks the holy war, who sharpen
their blade with their faith...
...who says that 'If we are here, there is
hope for the oppressed'!
Not Shepherd's son Yavlak Arslan's!
The state of those who come after
Oghuz Khan's most noble son Gün Khan's...
... most noble son Kayı's lineage!
I love you, brother.
Make your decision. Don't face me.
Did you do it? Where is Cerkutay?
Where is Cerkutay?
My bey, we took the dog from the Mongols.
We were bringing him to you but...
...Flatyos showed up.
-Where did Flatyos come from?
-They were so many, my bey...
...we were ambushed.
Ahh, lads. Ahh, lads.
What does Flatyos have to do with
Cerkutay?
Calm down, son. You can't solve it
with this anger.
If Nicola is behind this, it means that
they are united.
Time gets narrowed, enemies
come together...
...and we divide.
Cerkutay is here and this is our
second move, Flatyos.
I took him from Osman's alps,
not the Mongols.
This is even better, Flatyos.
So, Osman too is after Cerkutay.
His alps returned empty-handed, then.
-Indeed, Nikola.
-Good. Osman must be mad now.
He is coming to the point that I want.
Tell me, Cerkutay. Who was behind
the raven that set a trap for Osman?
Who knows?
You. You know it, Cerkutay. Come.
Shhh...
Look, we can do it this way too if you like.
I can make you talk in Roman ways.
Do it in Mongol ways.
Who was behind the trap?
Who was it?
Yavlak Arslan is coming, sir.
-What is Yavlak Arslan doing here?
-We'll see, Nicola.
Take this Mongol dog, bring my guest.
Flatyos, why are you never happy?
The soldiers that I asked from the emperor
is here. What are we waiting for?
Flatyos, you want us to raid a place every day,
fight with Kayıs, with Yavlak Arslan every day.
That only happens in tales. States stay
alive with the minds of smart people.
Putting your trust in a Cuman woman
doesn't sound so smart to me, Nicola.
Flatyos...
Flatyos, she will only do as we say and
make Kayı Tribe less habitable. That's all.
Enraged Osman will come to our foot, we won't
go to him. He will come to us, do you understand?
Then, we will crush him like stepping over a bug.
Then we will enter the defenseless Söğüt.
Do you get it?
I like tactics.
Thank you.
You are helpful, just like Osman Bey.
Osman Bey is like that.
He helps every oppressed he sees.
He is a valiant man.
He is.
What's wrong, I wonder?
Did you get lost, Hazal?
What was your intention in bringing
Aygül back to the tents?
It's Aygül's tribe. She returned
to her home.
So, you are sure that she won't
do anything crazy?
You should've thought that before
driving her crazy.
You made her crazy, I healed her.
Why did you bring that child? Won't Dündar
Bey go mad when he sees that child?
Won't he go crazy this time?
What can we do?
Everyone will pay for what they did, Hazal.
Come on.
Aygül.
I came to finish what was
left unfinished, Hazal.
Aygül, enough. Listen to me, you promised me.
You told me that you won't.
-Get out of my way!
-I'm talking to you, Aygül.
You promised me, lower your sword,
my girl.
Lower your sword, my girl.
She killed my mother!
-Aygül, enough! Enough, my girl.
-Get out of my way!
What did you promise me, Aygül?
I should go and check what's going on.
Go, go, don't worry about me.
I'm in your tent from the first day,
Osman Bey.
Stop! Stop!
Aygül, Aygül! I said stop!
Hazal, Hazal, stop!
Do you want to die? I trained her!
This is the end, Hazal.
-Enough!
-Let me go! Let me go!
Give me that. Take her.
I said, let me go!
It's not the end!
I will kill you and the ones
who saved you!
It's not the end! It's not the end!
How bad can a tribe go?
O' traveler. Where do you head to?
To the Red Apple.
(the idea of Turkic expansionism)
How happy the travelers of that path,
the ones who sharpen their blades with faith.
How happy the ones who ride
their horses in the dawn.
O' expecter!
Say it, for the blades that shine under
the dark of night! For the cities...
...that set fire by the speed of
our horses!
Which way is the Red Apple?
What is the difference...
between day and nigh, Osman Bey?
In Kayı Tribe...
It's always been night lately.
What is the reason?
Kayı's sun is sinking.
Death is at Our Bey Ertugrul Ghazi's door.
Is this the reason there is chaos?
Is this the reason nobody helps each other?
Brothers help each other.
They keep in touch.
- They don't know.
- What do you know, Osman Bey?
What is your aim?
I'll take what we lost back.
I'll punish the wild enemy.
I'll fight the enemy with my Alps who
want The Red Apple.
Until...
Until we become a state.
Our children shall see it.
They shall broaden their perspective.
Thank you.
May Allah help you.
You shall clash the enemy with your Alps..
who want The Red Apple.
When you rise your flag...
Noble Turks shall be with you.
Amin.
Osman Bey, your duty is difficult.
Don't give up.
Your duty is full of enemies.
Don't turn your back.
Your intention will enlight your way.
Don't give up.
May Allah help you.
Amin.
What are those Kuman troops about?
Yavlak. I thought we'd celebrate you being
Bey of the Beys.
You took Kulucahisar.
What are you still after?
Even that castle you conquered doesn't
belong to Kayıs, it belongs to me.
And as a result, Kayıs' land
is my property.
If you attack again, we'll fall out.
We won't fall out.
We should be clear to each other.
Let's talk about it.
I think we shouldn't threaten each other.
We should do business.
We should make each other rich.
Am I not right?
We should think about our future.
For instance...
We can talk about Cobanogullari and
Rome's future.
If Rome's future is conquering Karacahisar
and Sogut...
that means you have not a future.
Yavlak, if we go on threatening each
other like that...
no one can have a future in this land.
That evil Geyhatu leads both of us
by the nose.
Right?
Let me give you a secret.
I actually like Turks.
But those Kayıs...
How can I put this?
They annoy me.
I don't need your compassion, I
need your loyalty.
I am going to go back to Kastamonu.
Don't go behind my back.
I promise.
I won't backdoor you.
We only will talk face to face.
We'll see.
So you like Turks, Nicola?
Yes.
When they are dead.
I hope you didn't bring me here
just for this, Nicola.
No, I got you out of prison so you
can learn fighting.
There is no one who can beat me in
a duel in this land, Nicola.
Vladius.
Mother nature put the only thing
that defeat physical strength...
here.
The only thing that seperates us
from both Kayıs and Mongols is this.
We just need to use it.
Stop!
Do not eat!
This traitor poisoned the food.
Eat.
- You dog!
- Traitor!
She killed my mother.
Stop now! Stop!
I will kill if you threaten me with
my life!
Hazal Hatun, stop.
Calm down!
Hazal Hatun!
Calm down, Hazal Hatun!
Calm down.
Have a seat.
Drink this.
Hazal Hatun.
Calm down.
She'll try again. We can't wait.
We need to do something.
What needs to be done is clear!
You saw who opposes your husband Savcı
and backs Osman up.
I know, Hazal Hatun.
I want you to cooperate with you and
defeat them.
You were good with Bala.
What is it?
What happened?
It wouldn't work. While our Beys are in
this situation, we Hatuns can't be friends.
That's what I am talking about.
She wasn't the only
fish in the sea, my Lena.
Do you have to be that much private?
Ertugrul Ghazi's son Savcı Bey.
First time has to be like this.
We can't untie your eyes before you
untie your heart to us.
I am with anyone who wants Kayı Tribe's
salute.
Eyvallah, eyvallah. (thanks)
“God Almighty speaks the truth.”
Glorified is your Lord the Lord of Honour
and Power above what they claim!
[Saffah 37:180]
May Allah please you, Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Bey.
Thank Allah, my Bey.
Thank so much.
What is new?
Geyhatu arrived at the gates of our tribe
with his army, my Bey.
He asked for Mongke with his commanders.
Don't worry, my Bey.
We didn't let them damage our tribe.
What... what about my sons?
Osman has shown up, my Bey.
And Savcı brought Mongke.
Osman disobeyed you, but, my Bey...
He ruined Mongke's game and
saved his brother.
He saved us from Geyhatu trouble.
My Dark Osman.
I need to decide...
as soon as... possible...
Long live my Bey.
What is your aim, Savcı Bey?
What do you want for Kayıs?
When the night covers the sky...
we shouldn't campaign.
We should wait for the sun.
Let's see who is on our side!
I want to make sure that I aim
the real enemy.
We are few in number.
We should grow.
We have lots of enemiies.
I want to have less enemies.
I don't want my father Ertuğrul Ghazi's
relics to be wasted due to Mongols and Greeks.
So that we can have only one enemy.
And that brings us a successful campaign.
That's what I think.
Very well, Savcı Bey.
You have the soul of a fighter, Lena.
You aimed fast, decided fast.
I was lucky.
It's not about luck, it's about practice.
You know how to fight.
- Welcome, my Bey.
- Thank you.
I have chores to do.
I'll leave.
Of course, sure.
We will enter that castle today.
- We are ready, my Bey.
- The command is yours, my Bey.
Wait for my sign.
- Eyvallah, my Bey.
- Eyvallah, my Bey. (okay)
The only way to save your life is to
serve me.
You know this, right, Cerkutay?
It will cost dearly.
Tell me your price.
I want a slice of bloody meat.
Prepare me a bed, so I can rest.
And give me a beautiful woman.
Is that all?
Yes.
But I want a delicious woman so that
I can do my duty well.
This is the Mongol way, right?
Nikola.
The bait is taken.
Just as you estimated.
This news saved your life, Cerkutay.
But, you may not be this lucky next time.
This is the third step, Flatyos.
Osman will come to the castle with
Göktuğ and Boran.
This is such good news.
We need to tell Dündar Bey and Savcı Bey.
Lena...
Is it better for Osman to die in
that castle alone or...
is it better if Savcı and
Dündar stops him?
Come, Lena.
Come.
Eat some walnut, it'll be
good for your brain.
So, this is it.
When I save my father...
I'll shoot these arrows into
your mouth, Nikola.
Targun made it, I guess.
Osman... Nikola will be so
happy about this news.
Karayel seems so hungry, my Osman Bey.
It's Karayel, my valiant Ahmet.
He has been in so
many wars and he's still fine.
A horse is Turk's biggest comrade.
A brother. A confidant.
A wing, Ahmet.
My dad once had a horse.
He'd show me around with the horse.
He loved his horse.
He should come here.
I missed him so much!
So much!
My Ahmet.
I missed my father so much!
Don't cry, my valiant Ahmet.
Don't cry.
Now...
Your father raises a
horse for you in heaven.
Don't cry.
I'll make you ride horses.
My Bey.
We're ready.
Come on.
Stop crying.
You flame with vengeance for Osman and...
I hope it doesn't burn you, Flatyos.
Up!
We've started to reach
news from Kayı Tent.
I told you Osman would come here.
Is he coming?
Targun succeeded in her first duty.
Osman will come here.
Alone.
Nikola must have taken my message.
He'll set my father free.
- May it be easy.
- Thank you.
Cerkutay...
Cerkutay!
You're here!
You're mad enough to confront me.
I did what is asked for.
When they understood what I
did, I became a man of Nikola.
So?
For you, Yavlak Arslan.
Do you understand?
Nice.
Good.
Your loyalty filled me with tears.
You'll get what you deserve.
I'm looking for it.
Nikola, the lord of
Constantinople's Sultan...
and Savcı Bey, Ertuğrul Ghazi's son...
will discuss about war and..
I, Yavlak Arslan...
will---
eff...
eff...--
I'll make effort for it to happen.
It's better if everyone gathers
and discusses.
If the enemy wants peace...
you'll want peace and trust Allah.
I like to discuss.
Of course we should discuss.
Flatyos, when I waste Yavlak Arslan's
and...
Savcı Bey's time talking about peace...
you'll devastate Söğüt.
I like this kind of peace, Nikola.
Then, let's welcome Osman, Flatyos.
Everyone in the castle is
waiting for Osman's arrival.
I hope you come from this way, Osman.
They knew we were coming.
You know what to do.
Where do you think he'll come, Nikola?
It doesn't matter from where, if he comes.
- He doesn't know we're waiting.
- He won't come if he knows
Nice.
It's Osman.
He'll come.
He will come.
He will see.
He will die, Flatyos.
I want you to promise
me something, Nikola.
I will kill Osman.
- Now?
- Now. I'll kill him now.
Why?
Set the slaves free.
Or, I'll cut this dog's throat.
Don't let me go
if you don't kill me, Osman.
- Let him go.
- I'll send him when I'm done with him.
If a good hunter has a spear like this...
he can hunt a lion.
Because the lion can't pass the spear
and reach the hunter, Nikola.
But...
if the hunter realizes it and...
tries to play a game with the lion...
the lion will...
use its paws, Nikola.
Lion, huh? Lion.
Flatyos.
You sounded like you went through it.
Hunter of lions, huh?
I didn't know that.
Good.
Let's kill him when he comes, Nikola.
- We'll do it slowly, Flatyos.
Slowly.
What are you waiting for? Take him!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com